Finding Aid for the Phyllis Diller papers, 1934-2011 LSC.1893
UCLA Library Special Collections
Phyllis Diller papers
1934-2011
UCLA Library Special Collections
Diller, Phyllis
LSC.1893
51.5 Linear Feet (75 boxes)
This collection includes business papers, correspondence, sheet music, media, and memorabilia from the private collection of comedian and actress Phyllis Diller. Diller broke ground as one of the first and most prominent woman comedians through her stand-up act, films, television appearances, books, and records. Post-retirement in 2002, Diller wrote an autobiography titled Like a Lampshade in a Whorehouse: My Life in Comedy (2005), turned her hobby of drawing and painting into another career, and has continued to make appearances on television and in film.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Phyllis Diller, November 2007.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9967767243606533
Biography
Phyllis Ada Driver was born on July 17, 1917 in Lima, OH. She studied at the Sherwood Music Conservatory in Chicago, IL for three years, beginning in fall 1934. She married Sherwood Anderson Diller, and the couple and their children moved from Ypsilanti, MI to Alameda, CA in 1945. Diller began her career as writer and women's editor for the San Leandro News-Observer. From June 1951 to 1954, Diller's jobs included: head of newspaper and radio ad copy in the advertising office of Kahn's, a department store in Oakland, CA; copywriter, publicist, and continuity girl at the radio station KROW in Oakland, CA; and, finally, director of promotion and merchandising at KSFO radio in San Francisco, CA. Her copywriting was distinguished by its comedic flair.
Diller performed in several small and semi-professional venues before getting a lengthy gig at The Purple Onion, a nightclub in San Francisco, CA in March 1955. Following this successful run, she gave opening performances at The Purple Onion in Los Angeles, CA in summer 1956. In Los Angeles, Diller made her first national television appearance as a contestant on the NBC game show You Bet Your Life, hosted by Groucho Marx. Thereafter, she toured the country, performing in major nightclubs such as Mister Kelley's in Chicago, IL, The Blue Angel and The Bon Soir in New York, NY (where she worked with a young Barbra Streisand), The Crescendo in Los Angeles, CA, and The Fontainebleau in Miami Beach, FL. Diller's stand-up act pushed the envelope by lampooning women's roles in the 1950s and 1960s. In particular, she broke from the tradition set by male comedians who complained about their wives by creating a fictional husband, the ne'er-do-well Fang.
Around 1958, Diller made the first of many appearances on The Tonight Show and The Jack Paar Show, the latter for which she eventually became a writer. These appearances brought her heightened success, and led to her discovery by Bob Hope. Diller worked with Hope for decades, performing with him on 23 television specials, in the feature films Boy, Did I Get a Wrong Number! (1960), Eight on the Lam (1967), and The Private Navy of Sgt. O'Farrell (1968), and as part of his USO troupe in Vietnam in 1966. Diller's film work from this period also includes Splendor in the Grass (1962) and voice work in the Rankin/Bass animated film Mad Monster Party (1967). Beginning in the 1960s, Diller became a household name through many TV appearances featuring her stand-up act. She also starred in two short-lived TV series, the half-hour sitcom The Pruitts of Southhampton (later titled The Phyllis Diller Show, 1966-67) and the musical variety show The Beautiful Phyllis Diller Show (1968). From 1961-1970, Diller recorded five albums and published four books. She concluded the 1960s with her Broadway debut in Hello Dolly!
Recent film roles include voice work in Disney's A Bug's Life (1998) and the documentary The Aristocrats (2005). Recent television work includes recurring roles on the series Titus (2001-02), 7th Heaven (1999-2003), The Bold and the Beautiful (1999-2004), and The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius (2002-2004).
In May 1971, Diller drew upon her training as a pianist and made her debut in a concert with Pittsburgh Pops, initiating 10 years of work as a concert pianist. In the 1970s, 1980s, and 1990s, Diller continued frequent appearances on the stage and screen, and became known as one of the first celebrities to proudly admit to having had plastic surgery.
In 2002, Diller retired from stand-up comedy work. Her final performance, at the Suncoast Hotel in Las Vegas, NV, is captured in the documentary Good Night, We Love You (2006). Post-retirement, Diller wrote an autobiography titled Like a Lampshade in a Whorehouse: My Life in Comedy (2005), turned her hobby of drawing and painting into another career, and has continued to make appearances on television and in film.
Scope and Content
The collection includes correspondence (1969-2010, bulk 2005-2010); contracts and itineraries related to various stand-up, film, and television appearances; books of jokes and gags by Diller and other writers (dated 1964-1988); sheet music from Diller's time at Sherwood Music Conservatory, from her TV series The Beautiful Phyllis Diller Show (1968), and from other performances; extensive clippings from magazines and periodicals (dated 1957-2011, bulk 1992-2007); a representative wig and costume; filmed performances and television appearances (mostly on 16mm and 35mm); Diller's published books and record albums; playbills, programs and pamphlets for shows that Diller starred in or attended; and ephemera and souvenirs from Diller's career.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Correspondence
Job Folders and Other Activities
Jokes and Gags
Photographs
Sheet Music
Clippings
Publications
Playbills and programs
Ephemera and souvenirs
Media
Costumes
Items Removed from the Collection
The following films have been transferred to the UCLA Film and Television Archive:
Phyllis Diller on "The Jack Paar Show," November 12, 1969. 16mm.
Outtakes of local news feature story filmed when Diller appeared at The Century Room, 1960. 16mm.
"The Charlotte Peters Show" episode, March 7, 1963.
"The Tonight Show" segment, November 11, 1963. 16mm.
"Something to Say," September 12, 1964. 35mm.
"Girl Talk" episode, September 13, 1964. 35mm. 2 copies.
Phyllis Diller in "Showtime," July 1968. 16mm.
Unlabeled film reel, possibly copy of or content related to "Showtime."
"Work print: Dallas, Texas, Various Performances," March 1974. 16mm.
"Sound-Mag Trans. Dallas, Texas," July 18, 1974 (1 of 2). 16mm.
"Sound-Mag Trans. Dallas, Texas," July 18, 1974 (2 of 2). 16mm.
"Marriage Counselor," August 20, 1974. 35mm.
"Marriage Counselor" trims and cuts, August 20, 1974. 16mm.
"Phyllis Diller 'Kitchen Kween,'" undated. 16mm.
"The Hollywood Palace" episode, undated. 16mm.
"From Soup to Nuts," undated. 16mm.
"Teddy at the Throttle," undated. 16mm.
"The Adventurer," undated. 16mm.
"Celebration for Julie," undated. 16mm.
"Dubs of Phyllis Diller," undated. 35mm.
Unlabeled, undated film reel. 16mm.
Women comedians -- Archives.; Diller, Phyllis--Archives.
- Correspondence, 1969-2010
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes letters and cards to and from friends, family, and colleagues (including David Sedaris, Jerry Stiller, Anne Meara, Carol Channing, Florence Henderson, Roseanne Barr, Nancy Sinatra Sr., Arnold Schwarzenegger, Ronald Reagan, Nancy Reagan, and George W. Bush), invitations to events, and several fan letters.
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Reproductions of letters and cards from Diller to J.C. and Leona, Aunt Anna, and B.E. Harris (publisher of Diller's "Marriage Manual" and "Household Hints").
  - Correspondence, 1987-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Letters and cards to Diller from this period. All years are not covered.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Sidney Sheldon, Arnold Schwarzenegger, Joan Rivers, Jay Leno, Dom Deluise.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Helen Gurley Brown, Barbara Sinatra, Constance Towers, and Jack Gavin.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from John Lasseter, Jimmy Galanos, Senator Bob Graham.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Dick Clark, Renee Taylor, Rip Taylor.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Lucie Arnaz, Dom Deluise, and Richard Lewis.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Fred Willard, Loni Anderson, Debbie Reynolds, Tempest Storm, and Reba McEntire.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Nancy Reagan, Barbara Bush, and Larry Gelbart.
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller.
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Florence Henderson, Sidney Sheldon, and Richard Lewis.
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Joan Rivers, Rip Taylor, Helen Gurley Brown, Lynn Johnston, Dick Clark, George Chakiris, George Schlatter, and Sidney Sheldon.
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from John Gavin and Constance Towers, Tony Danza, Esther Williams, Helen L. Erfurt (roommate in Chicago).
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Lynn Johnston, Pat Rocco, and Henry Winkler.
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Barbra Streisand, Liz Smith, Cindy Adams, and Laura Bush.
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from John Forsythe, Billy Graham, and Bernie Kopell.
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Bob Anglund, Joan Anglund, Bernie Koppel, Nancy Sinatra Sr., Billy Stritch, and Lynn Johnston.
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from J.A. Perret (one of Diller's comedy writers).
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Nancy Sinatra Sr., and Rosie O' Donnell.
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Larry Storch, Lynn Johnston, and Constance Towers.
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Alexandra Sheldon (wife of Sidney), Elliott Gould, and Buzz Aldrin.
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Elliott Gould, Bob Anglund, Joan Anglund, and Ed McMahon.
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Jerry Stiller and Anne Meara.
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Dick Clark, Maya Angelou, Jerry Stiller, and Anne Meara.
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Nancy Reagan, Gene Perret, Jerry Stiller, and Anne Meara.
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Russ Tamblyn.
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Nancy Sinatra Sr.
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Crystal Gayle, Elliott Gould, and David Sedaris.
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Jack LaLanne, Anne Meara, Terry Black, and Randy Sparks.
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Anne Meara, Margaret Keane, and Lynn Johnston.
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Henry Winkler.
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Roseanne Barr, David Sedaris, George Booth, and John Gavin.
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from David Sedaris.
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Florence Henderson and David Sedaris.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Roseanne Barr, Tommy Tune, John Gavin, and Nanette Fabray.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Rita Rudner.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Carol Channing, Roseanne Barr, John Ratzenberger, Florence Henderson, Joanne Carson, Lynn Johnston, and George Lopez.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Debbie Reynolds.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Craig Ferguson.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Fred Willard, John Ratzenberger, Joanne Carson.
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Letters, cards, and invitations to Diller. Includes correspondence from Richard Lewis, and Betty White.
- Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995-2002
  Includes contracts, itineraries, and correspondence relating to Diller's stand- up acts, shows, and other performances and appearances, including Diller's final engagement. Note: Folder contents are sometimes housed in recycled manila envelopes with markings that do not correspond with their contents. See labels on the back of these envelopes for content description.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Includes renewal of contract for Inphomation Inc.; Harrah's Casino in Reno, NV; George and Barbara Bush's 50th Anniversary Celebration; "Battle of the Brains" (Kidder Foundation Fundraiser); Omni Netherlands Hotel in Cincinnati, OH.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Includes Phoenix Symphony Orchestra Auxiliary Committee in AZ; Cactus Pete's in Jackpot, NV; The Doug Mulray Show in Australia; The Loft Theatre in Dayton, OH.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Includes Bob Hope's Young Comedians TV Special; Monarch of the Seas (Royal Caribbean Cruise Line); "Women Who Lead" Awards: Papanicolaou Women's Corps for Cancer Research in Palm Beach, FL.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Includes Childhelp Luncheon in Ontario, CA; "Talk of the Town" TV show in Los Angeles, CA; Cinderella costume fittings in New York, NY; Jupiter Theatre in Jupiter, FL; "Mike & Maty" TV show in New York, NY.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Includes National Parkinson Foundation Luncheon in Palm Springs, FL; "In the Bag" TV Special, Los Angeles, CA; Congregation Israel Silver Spoon Gala in Saskatoon, CA; USO Fundraiser in San Francisco, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Includes Cerritos Center for the Performing Arts in Cerritos, CA; Volunteers of America "Honorary Advisory Board;" Beef 'n Boards Dinner Theatre in Indianapolis, IN; Plano Center in Plano, TX; Alameda County Fair in Pleasanton, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Includes "Bob & Dolores Hope: This Is Your Life" in Los Angeles, CA; "Talk Soup" TV appearance in Los Angeles, CA; Childhelp Fall Gala in Knoxville, TV; Sovereign of the Seas Royal Caribbean Cruise; 60th high school reunion in Lima, OH; Central Washington Fair in Yakima, WA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Includes Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Reno, NV; Riverside Resort in Laughlin, NV; Childcare Center of Antelope Valley Fundraiser in Lancaster, CA; Normandie Casino in Gardenia, CA; Sycuan Casino, El Cajon, CA; Jupiter Theatre in Jupiter, FL.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Includes Gala for L.I.F.E. in Palm Beach, FL; Metcalfs' Dinner Invitation in San Francisco, CA; trip to Santa Fe, NM.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Includes Museum of Television and Radio Gala in New York, NY; Sun City Community Center in Sun City, FL; Mahaffey Theatre in St. Petersburg, FL; Van Wezel Performing Arts in Sarasota, FL; Bailey Hall in Ft. Lauderdale, FL; Parkinson's Gala in Miami Beach, FL; Itineraries for Firan Foundation Fundraiser in Hamilton, Ontario, Canada; Nabors & Friends in Fort Worth, TX; Dollywood in Knoxville, TN; Monarch of the Seas Caribbean Cruise; Riverside Resort Hotel and Casino in Laughlin, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Includes Ticketmaster Online Interview; American Heart Association's Heart Ball in Los Angeles, CA; Visions International Women's Conference Lecture in Phoenix, AZ; Harrah's Casino in Reno, NV; "Cybill" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "Mancow's Morning Madness" Radio Show in Chicago; phone interview with "View" magazine in Hamilton, Ontario, Canada (possibly in relation to Firan Foundation Fundraiser, see folder 10); Bob Hope Roast Benefitting House Ear Institute in Los Angeles, CA; Rancho Los Amigos Foundation, Inc. in Long Beach, CA; French Foundation for Alzheimer Research in Los Angeles, CA (Art Linkletter honored).
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Monarch of the Seas Royal Caribbean Cruise; Hilton Hotel in Reno, NV; Dollywood in Knoxville, TN; Firan Foundation Fundraiser in Hamilton, Ontario, Canada.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Jim Nabors Gala in Fort Worth, TX; New York Friars Club Tribute in New York, NY; 1996-1997 itinerary; Tangier Supper Club in Akron, OH; San Francisco Symphony Pops Series in San Francisco, CA; Tangier Supper Club itineraries and phone interview schedules; Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas, NV; Honeywell Auditorium in Wabash, IN.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Rialto Square Theatre in Joliet, IL; phone interview schedule; Sovereign of the Seas Eastern Caribbean Cruise; Starlight Theatre Kansas City, MI; Bob Hope's birthday party in Los Angeles, CA; The Television Academy Celebrates Bob Hope in Los Angeles, CA; United Republican Finance Committee dinner for Dan Quayle in Los Angeles, CA; Patricia Goss arbitration correspondence; Toluca Lake Chamber of Commerce Dinner in Los Angeles, CA; Aid for AIDS Dinner in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Includes TV Guide phone interview; AMC's Fourth Annual Festival of Preservation in Los Angeles, CA; "The American Way" TV documentary; Starlight Theatre in Kansas City, MI; "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV show in Los Angeles, CA; 1996-1997 itinerary; Steakery Lounge and Ballroom in Longview, Washington; Sovereign of the Seas Eastern Caribbean Cruise; "Daytime for Awareness" celebrity recipe card collection; Monticello Hotel in Longview, WA; Fox TV piece on plastic surgery; "Style" TV series; Greenville Country Playhouse in Greenville, PA; "Splendor of the Seas" Royal Caribbean Cruise in Copenhagen and Oslo.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Includes "The Charles Grodin Show" appearance; interview for documentary on Pat Rocco; correspondence with Pope Theatre Company; dinner honoring Steve Allen and Jayne Meadows; "The Crook & Chase Show" TV series.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Request for a cover paragraph by Susan Horowitz for her book "Queens of Comedy," and book manuscript.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Westbury Music Fair in Westbury, NY; "The Crook and Chase Show" TV series in Nashville, TN; Splendour of the Seas Cruise in Copenhagen, Denmark and Oslo, Norway; National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences Event honoring Milton Berle in New York, NY; Indian Casino in Santa Ynez, CA; "You Don't Know Jack" voiceover agreement.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Art Show at Ambassador Galleries in New York, NY; Senior Citizen Group at The Garden State Arts Center in Handel, NJ; Toshiba computer product commercial; transcription of telephone answering machine messages; "The Museum of Television and Radio Presents: The Tradition of Stand Up Comedians" program; Norris Theatre for the PA's in Rolling Hills Estates, CA; Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Lake Tahoe, NV; "Message in a Bottle" fundraiser for home hospice care; phone interview schedules; The PCN Bank Arts Center at Garden State in Holmdel, NJ.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Lake Tahoe, NV; Los Angeles County Fair in Pomona, CA; Norris Cultural Center in St. Charles, IL (with Steve Allen); Curtis Peterson Auditorium in Lecanto, FL; HBO animation pilot TV series; "The Maury Povich Show" TV series; New York Friars Club Luncheon Honoring Kelsey Grammer; Indian City Commercial in Lincoln City, OR; Suicide and Crisis Center Benefit at Southern Methodist College in Dallas, TX; Grossmont Hospital Foundation in San Diego, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Includes McFarlin Auditorium in Dallas, TX; "Bugs" ("A Bug's Life") audition in Los Angeles, CA; Women's Expo in Madison, WI; "Bold and the Beautiful" contract; Childhelp USA in Scottsdale, AZ; Ruta Lee AIDS Benefit in Ft. Worth, TX.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Includes Kelsey Grammer roast in New York, NY; Mark II Dinner Theatre in Orlando, FL; Philharmonic Center for the Arts in Naples, FL; "Barrymore in Hollywood" TV program in Los Angeles, CA; "Bold and the Beautiful" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "Our House" TV interview in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)